{"test_questions": [[{"question": "For a 4-bit parallel adder, if the carry-in is connected to a logical HIGH, the result is:", "opta": "the same as if the carry-in is tied LOW since the least significant carry-in is ignored.", "optb": "that carry-out will always be HIGH.", "optc": "a one will be added to the final result.", "optd": "the carry-out is ignored.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the first thing you will need if you are going to use a macrofunction?", "opta": "A complicated design project", "optb": "An experienced design engineer", "optc": "Good documentation", "optd": "Experience in HDL", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Perform subtraction on each of the following binary numbers by taking the two's-complement of the number being subtracted and then adding it to the first number.01001\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00110000011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a000111", "opta": "01100\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a010011", "optb": "00110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a000101", "optc": "10110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a010101", "optd": "00111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a000100", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Solving \u201311 + (\u20132) will yield which two's-complement answer?", "opta": "1110 1101", "optb": "1111 1001", "optc": "1111 0011", "optd": "1110 1001", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Multiply the following binary numbers.   1010 \u00a0 1011 \u00a0 1001  \u00d70011 \u00a0 \u00d70111 \u00a0 \u00d71010", "opta": "0001\u00a0\u00a01110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00100\u00a0\u00a01101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01011", "optb": "0001\u00a0\u00a01110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00100\u00a0\u00a01100\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01010", "optc": "0001\u00a0\u00a01110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00100\u00a0\u00a01101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01010", "optd": "0001\u00a0\u00a01101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00100\u00a0\u00a01101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01010", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Add the following BCD numbers.   0110 \u00a0 0111 \u00a0 1001  0101 \u00a0 1000 \u00a0 1000", "opta": "0000\u00a0\u00a01011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a01111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a00001", "optb": "0001\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a00001", "optc": "0000\u00a0\u00a01011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a01111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a00111", "optd": "0001\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a00111", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Add the following hexadecimal numbers.    3C \u00a0 14 \u00a0 3B  +25 \u00a0 +28 \u00a0 +DC", "opta": "60\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a03C\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0116", "optb": "62\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a03C\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0118", "optc": "61\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a03C\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0117", "optd": "61\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a03D\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0117", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Solve this BCD problem: 0100 + 0110 =", "opta": "00010000BCD", "optb": "00010111BCD", "optc": "00001011BCD", "optd": "00010011BCD", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What are constants in VHDL code?", "opta": "Fixed numbers represented by a name", "optb": "Fixed variables used in functions", "optc": "Fixed number types", "optd": "Constants do not exist in VHDL code.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The 2's-complement system is to be used to add the signed binary numbers 11110010 and 11110011. Determine, in decimal, the sign and value of each number and their sum.", "opta": "\u2013113 and \u2013114, \u2013227", "optb": "\u201314 and \u201313, \u201327", "optc": "\u201311 and \u201316, \u201327", "optd": "\u201327 and \u201313, \u201340", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The most commonly used system for representing signed binary numbers is the:", "opta": "2's-complement system.", "optb": "1's-complement system.", "optc": "10's-complement system.", "optd": "sign-magnitude system.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the major difference between half-adders and full-adders?", "opta": "Nothing basically; full-adders are made up of two half-adders.", "optb": "Full adders can handle double-digit numbers.", "optc": "Full adders have a carry input capability.", "optd": "Half adders can handle only single-digit numbers.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The decimal value for E16 is:", "opta": "1210", "optb": "1310", "optc": "1410", "optd": "1510", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Fast-look-ahead carry circuits found in most 4-bit full-adder circuits:", "opta": "determine sign and magnitude", "optb": "reduce propagation delay", "optc": "add a 1 to complemented inputs", "optd": "increase ripple delay", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Add the following hex numbers: 011016 + 1001016", "opta": "1012016", "optb": "1002016", "optc": "1112016", "optd": "0012016", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The binary subtraction 0 \u2013 0 =", "opta": "difference = 0borrow = 0", "optb": "difference = 1borrow = 0", "optc": "difference = 1borrow = 1", "optd": "difference = 0borrow = 1", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Convert each of the decimal numbers to 8-bit two's-complement form and then perform subtraction by taking the two's-complement and adding.", "opta": "0001\u00a0\u00a00011", "optb": "0000\u00a0\u00a01110", "optc": "0010\u00a0\u00a01110", "optd": "1110\u00a0\u00a00000", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Adding in binary, a decimal 26 + 27 will produce a sum of:", "opta": "111010", "optb": "110110", "optc": "110101", "optd": "101011", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Convert each of the following signed binary numbers (two's-complement) to a signed decimal number.00000101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a011111100\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a011111000", "opta": "\u20135\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0+4\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0+8", "optb": "+5\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u20134\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u20138", "optc": "\u20135\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0+252\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0+248", "optd": "+5\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u2013252\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u2013248", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many basic binary subtraction operations are possible?", "opta": "4", "optb": "3", "optc": "2", "optd": "1", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If [A] = 1011 1010, [B] = 0011 0110, and [C] = [A] \u0095 [B], what is [C 4..2] in decimal?", "opta": "1", "optb": "2", "optc": "3", "optd": "4", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Using 4-bit adders to create a 1See Section 6-bit adder:", "opta": "requires 16 adders.", "optb": "requires 4 adders.", "optc": "requires the carry-out of the less significant adder to be connected to the carry-in of the next significant adder.", "optd": "requires 4 adders and the connection of the carry out of the less significant adder to the carry-in of the next significant adder.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When performing subtraction by addition in the 2's-complement system:", "opta": "the minuend and the subtrahend are both changed to the 2's-complement.", "optb": "the minuend is changed to 2's-complement and the subtrahend is left in its original form.", "optc": "the minuend is left in its original form and the subtrahend is changed to its 2's-complement.", "optd": "the minuend and subtrahend are both left in their original form.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The two's-complement system is to be used to add the signed numbers 11110010 and 11110011. Determine, in decimal, the sign and value of each number and their sum.", "opta": "\u201314 and \u201313, \u201327", "optb": "\u2013113 and \u2013114, 227", "optc": "\u201327 and \u201313, 40", "optd": "\u201311 and \u201316, \u201327", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When 1100010 is divided by 0101, what is the decimal remainder?", "opta": "2", "optb": "3", "optc": "4", "optd": "6", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One way to make a four-bit adder perform subtraction is by:", "opta": "inverting the output.", "optb": "inverting the carry-in.", "optc": "inverting the B inputs.", "optd": "grounding the B inputs.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the most important operation in binary-coded decimal (BCD) arithmetic?", "opta": "addition", "optb": "subtraction", "optc": "multiplication", "optd": "division", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The range of positive numbers when using an eight-bit two's-complement system is:", "opta": "0 to 64", "optb": "0 to 100", "optc": "0 to 127", "optd": "0 to 256", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What are the two types of basic adder circuits?", "opta": "sum and carry", "optb": "half-adder and full-adder", "optc": "asynchronous and synchronous", "optd": "one- and two's-complement", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The truth table for a full adder is shown below. What are the values of X, Y, and Z?", "opta": "X = 0, Y = 1, Z = 1", "optb": "X = 1, Y = 1, Z = 1", "optc": "X = 1, Y = 0, Z = 1", "optd": "X = 0, Y = 0, Z = 1", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A half-adder circuit would normally be used each time a carry input is required in an added circuit.", "opta": "True", "optb": "False", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If B[7..0] = 10100101, what is the value of B[6..2]?", "opta": "10100", "optb": "01001", "optc": "10010", "optd": "00101", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many inputs must a full-adder have?", "opta": "4", "optb": "2", "optc": "5", "optd": "3", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "", "opta": "10011110", "optb": "01211110", "optc": "000100000100", "optd": "001000001000", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Determine the two's-complement of each binary number.00110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a000011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a011101", "opta": "11001\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a011100\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a000010", "optb": "00111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a000010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a000010", "optc": "00110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a000011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a011101", "optd": "11010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a011101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a000011", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Solve this binary problem: 01110010 \u2013 01001000 =", "opta": "00011010", "optb": "00101010", "optc": "01110010", "optd": "00111100", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What distinguishes the look-ahead-carry adder?", "opta": "It is slower than the ripple-carry adder.", "optb": "It is easier to implement logically than a full adder.", "optc": "It is faster than a ripple-carry adder.", "optd": "It requires advance knowledge of the final answer.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Solve this binary problem:", "opta": "1001", "optb": "0110", "optc": "0111", "optd": "0101", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Half-adders can be combined to form a full-adder with no additional gates.", "opta": "True", "optb": "False", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Perform the following hex subtraction: ACE16 \u2013 99916 =", "opta": "23516", "optb": "13516", "optc": "03516", "optd": "33516", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is correct for full adders?", "opta": "Full adders have the capability of directly adding decimal numbers.", "optb": "Full adders are used to make half adders.", "optc": "Full adders are limited to two inputs since there are only two binary digits.", "optd": "In a parallel full adder, the first stage may be a half adder.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Convert each of the signed decimal numbers to an 8-bit signed binary number (two's-complement).+7\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u20133\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u201312", "opta": "0000\u00a0\u00a00111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01111\u00a0\u00a01101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01111\u00a0\u00a00100", "optb": "1000\u00a0\u00a00111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00111\u00a0\u00a01101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00111\u00a0\u00a00100", "optc": "0000\u00a0\u00a00111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a00011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a01100", "optd": "0000\u00a0\u00a00111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01000\u00a0\u00a00011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01000\u00a0\u00a01100", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is one disadvantage of the ripple-carry adder?", "opta": "The interconnections are more complex.", "optb": "More stages are required to a full adder.", "optc": "It is slow due to propagation time.", "optd": "All of the above.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Solve this binary problem: 01000110 \u00f7 00001010 =", "opta": "0111", "optb": "10011", "optc": "1001", "optd": "0011", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Divide the following binary numbers.", "opta": "0000\u00a0\u00a00010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a00010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01000\u00a0\u00a01111", "optb": "0000\u00a0\u00a00010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a00010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a00100", "optc": "0000\u00a0\u00a00011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a00010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a00100", "optd": "0000\u00a0\u00a00010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a00010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a00100", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Convert the decimal numbers 275 and 965 to binary-coded decimal (BCD) and add. Select the BCD code groups that reflect the final answer.", "opta": "1101 1110 1010", "optb": "1110 1010 1110", "optc": "0001 0010 0100 0000", "optd": "0010 0011 0100 0000", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When multiplying 13 \u00d7 11 in binary, what is the third partial product?", "opta": "1011", "optb": "00000000", "optc": "100000", "optd": "100001", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many BCD adders would be required to add the numbers 97310 + 3910?", "opta": "3", "optb": "4", "optc": "5", "optd": "6", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The selector inputs to an arithmetic/logic unit (ALU) determine the:", "opta": "selection of the IC", "optb": "arithmetic or logic function", "optc": "data word selection", "optd": "clock frequency to be used", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is wrong, if anything, with the circuit in the given figure based on the logic analyzer display accompanying the circuit?", "opta": "The CO terminal is shorted to ground.", "optb": "The S1 output is shorted to Vcc.", "optc": "The P1 input is not being added into the total.", "optd": "Nothing is wrong; the circuit is functioning correctly.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the statements below best describes the given figure?", "opta": "Half-carry adder; Sum = 0, Carry = 1", "optb": "Half-carry adder; Sum = 1, Carry = 0", "optc": "Full-carry adder; Sum = 1, Carry = 0", "optd": "Full-carry adder; Sum = 1, Carry = 1", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An 8-bit register may provide storage for two's-complement codes within which decimal range?", "opta": "+128 to \u2013128", "optb": "\u2013128 to +127", "optc": "+128 to \u2013127", "optd": "+127 to \u2013127", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A full-adder adds ________.", "opta": "two single bits and one carry bit", "optb": "two 2-bit binary numbers", "optc": "two 4-bit binary numbers", "optd": "two 2-bit numbers and one carry bit", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The carry propagation delay in 4-bit full-adder circuits:", "opta": "is cumulative for each stage and limits the speed at which arithmetic operations are performed", "optb": "is normally not a consideration because the delays are usually in the nanosecond range", "optc": "decreases in direct ratio to the total number of full-adder stages", "optd": "increases in direct ratio to the total number of full-adder stages, but is not a factor in limiting the speed of arithmetic operations", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An input to the mode pin of an arithmetic/logic unit (ALU) determines if the function will be:", "opta": "one's-complemented", "optb": "arithmetic or logic", "optc": "positive or negative", "optd": "with or without carry", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Could the sum output of a full-adder be used as a two-bit parity generator?", "opta": "Yes", "optb": "No", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In VHDL, what is a GENERATE statement?", "opta": "The start statement of a program", "optb": "Not used in VHDL or ADHL", "optc": "A way to get the computer to generate a program from a circuit diagram", "optd": "A way to tell the compiler to replicate several components", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Binary subtraction of a decimal 15 from 43 will utilize which two's complement?", "opta": "101011", "optb": "110000", "optc": "011100", "optd": "110001", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is the primary advantage of using binary-coded decimal (BCD) instead of straight binary coding?", "opta": "Fewer bits are required to represent a decimal number with the BCD code.", "optb": "BCD codes are easily converted from decimal.", "optc": "the relative ease of converting to and from decimal", "optd": "BCD codes are easily converted to straight binary codes.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "How many inputs must a full-adder have?", "opta": "2", "optb": "3", "optc": "4", "optd": "5", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Convert each of the decimal numbers to two's-complement form and perform the addition in binary.  +13\u00a0\u201310 add \u20137\u00a0add +15", "opta": "0001\u00a0\u00a00100\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a00101", "optb": "0000\u00a0\u00a00110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a01001", "optc": "0000\u00a0\u00a00110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00000\u00a0\u00a00101", "optd": "1111\u00a0\u00a00110\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01111\u00a0\u00a00101", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Add the following binary numbers.   0010 0110 \u00a0 0011 1011 \u00a0 0011 1100  +0101 0101 \u00a0 +0001 1110 \u00a0 +0001 1111", "opta": "0111 1011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00100\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01011", "optb": "0111 1011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01001\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01011", "optc": "0111 0111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01001\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01011", "optd": "0111 0111\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00100\u00a0\u00a00001\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a01011", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The carry propagation delay in full-adder circuits:", "opta": "is normally not a consideration because the delays are usually in the nanosecond range.", "optb": "decreases in a direct ratio to the total number of FA stages.", "optc": "is cumulative for each stage and limits the speed at which arithmetic operations are performed.", "optd": "increases in a direct ratio to the total number of FA stages but is not a factor in limiting the speed of arithmetic operations.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the difference between a full-adder and a half-adder?", "opta": "Half-adder has a carry-in.", "optb": "Full-adder has a carry-in.", "optc": "Half-adder does not have a carry-out.", "optd": "Full-adder does not have a carry-out.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The summing outputs of a half- or full-adder are designated by which Greek symbol?", "opta": "omega", "optb": "theta", "optc": "lambda", "optd": "sigma", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Subtract the following hexadecimal numbers.    47 \u00a0 34 \u00a0 FA  \u201325 \u00a0 \u20131C \u00a0 \u20132F", "opta": "22\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a018\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0CB", "optb": "22\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a017\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0CB", "optc": "22\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a019\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0CB", "optd": "22\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a018\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0CC", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What is the correct output of the adder in the given figure, with the outputs in the order:", "opta": "10111", "optb": "11101", "optc": "01101", "optd": "10011", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Solve this binary problem:", "opta": "11001001", "optb": "10010000", "optc": "01101110", "optd": "01110110", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The BCD addition of 910 and 710 will give initial code groups of 1001 + 0111. Addition of these groups generates a carry to the next higher position. The correct solution to this problem would be to:", "opta": "ignore the lowest order code group because 0000 is a valid code group and prefix the carry with three zeros", "optb": "add 0110 to both code groups to validate the carry from the lowest order code group", "optc": "disregard the carry and add 0110 to the lowest order code group", "optd": "add 0110 to the lowest order code group because a carry was generated and then prefix the carry with three zeros", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Subtract the following binary numbers.   0101 1000 \u00a0 1010 0011 \u00a0 1101 1110  \u20130010 0011 \u00a0 \u20130011 1000 \u00a0 \u20130101 0111", "opta": "0011\u00a0\u00a00100\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00110\u00a0\u00a01010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01000\u00a0\u00a00110", "optb": "0011\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00110\u00a0\u00a01011\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01000\u00a0\u00a00111", "optc": "0011\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00110\u00a0\u00a01010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01000\u00a0\u00a00111", "optd": "0011\u00a0\u00a00101\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a00110\u00a0\u00a01010\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a01000\u00a0\u00a00110", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Why is a fast-look-ahead carry circuit used in the 7483 4-bit full-adder?", "opta": "to decrease the cost", "optb": "to make it smaller", "optc": "to slow down the circuit", "optd": "to speed up the circuit", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Find the 2's complement of \u20131101102.", "opta": "1101002", "optb": "1010102", "optc": "0010012", "optd": "0010102", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "What logic function is the sum output of a half-adder?", "opta": "AND", "optb": "exclusive-OR", "optc": "exclusive-NOR", "optd": "NAND", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The binary adder circuit is designed to add ________ binary numbers at the same time.", "opta": "2", "optb": "4", "optc": "6", "optd": "8", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}